(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T04:25:19.430051",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
Takin' you all below, takin' you all below
Don't, don't know me, irresistible
Takin' you all below, below we go
They think they want it?
(Huh?)
They wanna get, get down
We take 'em down
(Down, down)
Queendom in the borderline
Run it, no surprise
You ain't gonna win, but you can try
Told ya, you got no luck
End up in my lineup
Listen, listen
Run, oh hide and scream out
Already locked ya up
Fool's games you always play
Call me corrupt, won't hear anything
Aiming my sight down right on your heart
Throwin' the keys out, shut down
I~
(Justice, just like that)
Love it, the forbidden
You're never forgiven
(Justice, get, get that)
Not one to just forget
We got 'em
The higher I rise
Down further you dive
Standin' on the edge
Don't know me, unpredictable, typical you
Got nowhere to go
Show you somethin' real, my level no you'll never know
As above so below, you should know
Dudurudurudu (We got it!)
Run in the light, oh my dio
What's wrong, what's right?
Rushin' in a fantasy, wannabe disease
Sure that you won't ever make it out
Eyes follow now
Do it, do it
New target locked on it now (now)
Enemies? Girl, I lost count (uh)
See your guilty heart
We're not gonna stop
It's just the start
Ooh~
Get down, get darada
(Like it like that? Run it like that)
Get down
Get down, down, down, down
Hey!
Takin' me up, up, up, let's go
Goin' above, go below
Told ya, you already know
don’t, don’t know me unpredictable
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable,
takin’ you all below, takin’ you all be-
takin' you all below, takin' you all be-
don’t don’t know me, irresistible
don't don't know me, irresistible,
takin’ you all below, below we go
takin' you all below, below we go.
they think they want it?
(huh?)
they wanna ge-get down
we take ’em down
we take 'em down,
(down down)
queendom in the borderline
run it, no surprise
you ain’t gonna win, but you can try
You ain't gonna win, but you can try.
told ya, you got no luck
end up in my lineup
listen, listen
run oh hide and scream out
already locked ya up
fool’s games you always play
Fool's games you always play,
call me corrupt, won’t hear anything
call me corrupt, won't hear anything.
aiming my sight down right on your heart
throwin’ the keys out, shut down
throwin' the keys out, shut down.
i~
(justice, just like that)
love it, the forbidden
you’re never forgiven
you're never forgiven.
(justice, get get that)
not one to just forget
we got ’em
We got 'em!
the higher i rise
down further you dive
standin’ on the edge, don’t know me, unpredictable, typical you
Standin' on the edge, don't know me, unpredictable, typical you,
got nowhere to go
show you somethin’ real, my level no you’ll never know, as above so below, you should know
Show you somethin' real, my level no you'll never know, as above so below, you should know.
dudurudurudu
(we got it!)
run in the light, oh my dio
what’s wrong, what’s right?
what's wrong, what's right?
rushin’ in a fantasy
Rushin' in a fantasy,
wannabe disease
sure that you won’t ever make it out
Sure that you won't ever make it out,
eyes follow now
do it, do it
new target locked on it now (now)
enemies? girl, i lost count (uh)
see your guilty heart
we’re not gonna stop
we're not gonna stop,
it’s just the start
it's just the start.
ooh~
get down get darada (like it like that? run it like that)
get down down down down
hey!
takin’ me up up up let’s go
Takin' me up up up let's go,
goin’ above, go below
goin' above, go below.
told ya, you already know
don’tcha?
don'tcha?
they know it!
Hello everyone!
Hello!
At last, we are in 3D,
and we've gotten to perform ABOVE BELOW!
Do you like it? Do you like our performance?
Did you like our performance?
If you really like the shot from it, remember we have a hashtag, #Justice3D,
post it on social media and we'd love to see that!
Ta-da!
Now that we're finally in 3D, guys,
we want to do an introduction, but full energy with poses!
Cool poses!
Cool poses! We have poses, cool poses!
Alright, okay.
Roses are red, the fire of my heart is blue,
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the harbinger of order, leader of Justice!
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame.
Lovely to see you, to see you.
Lovely!
And have... so cool!
So cool! Whoa!
Gigi, look at her tail! Look at her tail! Look at her tail!
Look at her cable! Look at her cable! Look at her cable!
Cecilia Immergreen, from hololive English Justice!
Darn it! Fist bump! Fist bump!
On the official Hololive English channel.
It really is! It really is!
Hi everyone, it's me, Cecilia Immergreen from hololive English Justice, spin to win!
Twisting! Yay! Woo!
In 3D! And then, of course, we have our...
Ta-da, everyone! This is Raora Panthera from hololive English Justice! Big cut means big trouble!
Big trouble!
Yay! And everyone...
take a look at where we are now!
Ta-da! Woah! So spacious! So spacious! Woah!
Touch-designed! Tail-wrapped! She's naked!
I guess I gotta take... take off my skirt.
What? What is she doing? Walk away! Walk away!
Oh my gosh, I can't look at her! She's naked! Uh!
She's naked? Okay.
It's not naked.
This don't got, you're bearing very normal pants.
I see, I see, it's understandable.
Alright, that was wrong. That felt wrong.
Well, maybe you shouldn't have done it.
Can you see a door? Yes, you should have a door.
HR? HR? Calling HR!
Liz! Liz! What's happening now?
They're fighting again.
Woah! As usual. Woah! Stop fighting! Get on your places and shut up!
So guys, what's what's the what's the plan for today? Do we have, hmm, how about we, how about we...
So guys, what's the plan for today? Do we have... how about we... how about we...
I suggest ice cream.
Ice cream? How about we get some ice cream? Liz, ice cream?
Well, it's our ice cream debut, so I think it'd be nice to do something fun, of course.
Yes, ice cream! Ice cream is fun! But, I think...
We should play a game, maybe a game?
Ooh.
And then whoever wins gets ice cream. Ice cream.
ATTEEEEEEEEEENTION!
ATTENNNNNNENTION!
Up and at 'em, maggots! It's time to get to work!
No slacking off while I, Sergeant Smokey, am busting my scales off for Justice!
Heh?
Heyyy, long time no see you! How are you doing?
Heyyy, long time no see! How are you doing?
"Heeey"?! GET IT TOGETHER!!!
Now line up and stand at attention, peabrains!!
Oh, okay, calm down, Liz.
Okay, calm down, Liz.
Let's just do as Smokey says. It's his first big appearance.
Let's just do what Smokey says. It's his first big appearance.
Though he seems pretty fired up.
Okay, I will do it for you, Liz.
All right, let's go. How about one? Oh, hey Liz.
All right, let's go.
Enough talking! Do I make myself clear?!
Sir, yes, sir!
I can't hear you! Sir, yes, sir!
Show me your war face! Yeeeeaaah!
Headquarters tells me you've been getting sloppy, so I'm here to set things straight!
Sloppy?
I've got a few brutal challenges lined up to whip your sorry hides into shape!
Wait, a smoke alarm? Has it always been there?
Yeah, have they always been there?
Whoa. Let's go look. Let's go look.
Oh, a fridge? Woah! Woah!
Alright, read the rules!
Here we are.
Let's see what it says. Think Fast, Move Faster!
This is a training exercise for both your brain and your body.
Use the giant keyboard to quickly input the answer to the question shown on the projector.
The trial consists of 10 questions per person. If you're stuck, you can skip and answer it later.
Correct answers with more letters will get higher points. Ooh, alright, yeah.
Correct answers with more letters will get higher points.
Fur my last email.
Let's see who can rack up the most points in 90 seconds!
In 90 seconds?
No whining! Cecilia, you go first! Get in there!
Okay, I'll go first.
Get out of my way! Get out of my way! Get out of my way!
Cecilia, it's up to you.
Watch this guy, stone worry. Don't worry, don't worry, I got this.
Are you really ready?
How ready are you? Are you really, really ready?
We're going to escalate. I got to write the C-letter.
All right, let's get started. You're like on 90 seconds. Okay, okay, okay, I'm ready, I'm ready, I'm ready.
All right, let's get started. You've got 90 seconds.
Three, two, one, go!
What is Gigi's last name?
M, U, R, I, N. Enter! You're in!
A. Murin!
One of Raora's goals as an idol is to publish an [blank] book!
One of Raora's goals as an idol is to publish a [blank] book!
Scrap book!
Scrapbook!
Don't you? Scrap?
Elizabeth is from Great [blank]!
Wait, where am I from?
E, X, A, R, D, I, A. Enter! You have one minute!
A. Exardia!
Who wrote the play Romeo and Juliet? Answer with the full name.
Full name! With his first name! W, I, L, L, I, A, M.
Full name! S, H, A, K, E, S, P, E, A, R, E.
Come on! H, U, M, O, R. Full name! Got this! Just two different E, E, S.
William Shakespeare! You're almost there!
You got this! S, H, A, K, E, S, P, E, A, R, E, again!
I don't know. I don't know.
Enter! A. William Shakespeare!
How many hearts does a fish typically have?
Oh, I don't know. Oh, hey, ten.
Can't say that word! Enter! Wait, you have...
You have five seconds left, quick!
Granny Smith and Fuji are types of which fruit?
Wow, apple!
A, P, P, L, E. Enter!
Nice try! Nice try. Nice try.
Okay, that's the only exercise I'm going to do for today.
How many points did I get?
Let me calculate in my brain. Go, did you go? Do a quick math.
Let me calculate in my brain. Do a quick math.
Points! 9! Wow, that's a pretty good score! Carry on, not to end on a good start.
9 points! Wow, that's a pretty good score! Carry on, not to end on a good start.
Next challenger, MOVE IT!!
I guess I'll tap in.
Let her show you who's the...
Let her show you who's the—
Oh.
all type-in.
Oh, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
Wait, what? Door!
Whoa, oh!
We're gonna leave her here.
Yeah!
Wait, wait, wait!
You can do it!
All right.
I, the leader of Justice, shall go next.
Let's get started. Dez, are you ready?
Yes. Count me in.
Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
All right. One of Raora's nicknames is...
Big...
C-A-T.
C-A-T!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Enter!
Finally, someone who knows my questions!
All right. Cecilia likes to drink...
T-E-A!
She likes to drink coffee!
No, no, coffee!
Gigi's fans are called...
Wait, why is that long?
G-R-E...
Uh-oh.
M? That's a long...
Oh, that's a long word.
That's a long...
L-I-N...
G-E-R...
M-E-N...
GREMLINGS!
That's a trick question!
It's gremurins!
That's the real name.
Really?
Yeah, cuz...
Who painted the Mona Lisa?
Next question!
What do you call a group of lions?
P-I...
I don't know. Lion?
Big group of lions?
I...
Cat? Pride?
Pride cat?
P-R-I...
D-E...
Enter! Go, go, go!
Nice! Good job!
Which country is famous for inventing pizza?
The Romans! The Roman Empire!
I know this one.
I don't think this is right.
Enter!
I think it's the Roman Empire!
Roman Empire!
What is the fear of confined spaces called?
What is that?
Does it exist?
Scared. Next!
I don't even have enough time anyway.
Of course!
How do you feel? How do you feel?
Are you tired?
What's my score?
What's my score, guys?
I think your score's being calculated.
What's my score?
In my brain, in my brain of brains.
I'm carry the one. It was four.
Got four points.
Four points?
What the frick!
That was really good.
That energy is fine.
No, it's—it's because they tricked you with gremurins.
Cat girl! Let me see your typing paws!
Okay, I got it, I got it, I got it!
You got this, Raora!
Let's get started.
Okay.
Three!
Two!
One! Go!
What color is the flame on Elizabeth's chest?
Don't look! Don't look! Don't look! Don't look!
Don't look at her!
You!
You're shy!
Oh, no! It's E!
Enter B-L-U-E!
A. Blue!
What is the name of Gigi's mascot?
Wait, again?
Oh, no! Gigi's mascot!
Gigi's mascot!
P-O-P-O!
Enter P-O-P-O!
A. Popo!
What is Cecilia's last name?
I-M-M...
Oh, go, go!
E-R...
She forgot it, didn't she?
Okay. E!
Don't be mean! E!
Q-U-A-R-T...
What's a Q-W-E-R-T-Y keyboard?
Wait, Raora!
The second one!
Okay, go, go, go, go, go!
Enter!
A. Immergreen!
Okay. Okay.
Keep up, too many words. Keep up, keep up.
How many legs do insects have?
Keep up!
What kind of reptile is a Komodo dragon?
Keep up! I don't know any!
This is a W-A-S-P.
What is the name of the layer of gases surrounding the Earth?
Skip! Skip! Skip! Skip! Skip!
Keep, keep! It's too long! She don't want spell them!
What is the highest female vocal range called?
Oh, oh, oh, oh! You got this one!
The one, two, three, four!
I don't know any.
Good job!
I'm sorry!
Gigi, score!
Calculating, calculating.
10 right? Is it 10 right?
20? 20?
It was four.
Why are you sad?
Why are you sad? You tied with me. I got a really...
I got a really good score.
Don't you think I did really well? Yeah, don't you think I did well?
I—I—I don't...
I think there is a miscalculation here.
Congratulations!
Okay, okay. Next one, next one.
Okay.
Oh, yes. I guess it is me.
What if they ask really hard questions?
I'm scared.
You should be scared.
I'm scared of really hard questions.
Okay, are you ready, Gigi?
I'm ready!
Okay, let's get started.
Three, two, one, started!
Which flower best represents Elizabeth?
Roses! Skip!
What? Wait, wait, wait! Keep it!
Uh, no, it's got it.
Stop you!
A!
Enter!
Win!
What?
B-H!
A!
T-T!
O!
I!
Enter!
Chattino!
Ah, okay. Come on!
Come on!
S-I-X-A-A!
C!
Y-Y-N!
E-W!
N-O!
T-O-N!
O-N!
Enter!
Isaac Newton!
This feels way shorter than
Will Shakespeare!
Wait!
King of fruits!
Only one point!
Skip, only one point!
What the...
Oh, you got this! You got this!
Big ones!
Sick get!
I don't care! Okay! I don't care!
Skip! I don't care!
What gas do plants release...
Heh.
Think about it!
Think, Gigi, think!
Think, Gigi, think! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Is it gas or air?
Oxygen!
I think it's gas.
Ah...
You got this! You got this!
X-7!
Y-G!
E-O!
N-Enter!
No!
Oxygen!
Okay, okay, okay!
Isaac Newton versus William Shakespeare!
And they give the same amount of points?
That's nuts! I think that's...
That's not fair!
Lookies doing smokey!
Yeah, I think it's unfair to
play a game where we need to read!
That's not well, anyways,
you want to know your score?
You want to know your score?
What's my score? 20, Gigi?
What is it?
It's 10 points!
Good job, Gigi!
Good job, Gigi! This is why you are a member of Justice!
Hmff... Looks like you maggots still need some serious training...
Hmph... Looks like you maggots still need some serious training...
Alright, time for the second trial, you knuckleheads.
I got some special training gear for you!
Ooh!
Don't hit me! Don't hit me!
Abuse!
What is this?
Ah, yes, we are going to have a duel!
Why is this just rules?
Rule one of Dizzy Combat:
Split into two groups!
And then one member on each team is blindfolded!
And we have to spin five times!
And after you spin five times, you will face off against each other in an epic sword battle!
Through the dark, while being blindfolded!
The remaining teammate that is not blindfolded must guide the other player to hit them!
It's like a coop game! Okay, okay.
First, before you pick a team, the points for each target: head - 5 points, each arm - 2 points, each knee - 3 points each. Okay, that makes sense. Got it.
Elizabeth! Gigi! Time for you dirtbags to beat the snot out of each other!
She's on the ground!
On your left! On your left!
Okay, okay. Left, left.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Hit it! Hit it!
Good! That's it! That's it!
Yes! Yes! Yes! You almost got it.
Aim for the leg!
Keep on hitting! Keep on hitting!
That's nice! That's nice!
That's really well! Keep on hitting!
Keep on hitting! Keep on hitting! Keep on hitting!
Aim for the head! Aim for the head!
Okay, okay.
You did it!
I don't know. You did it! You did it!
Yeah, I think you absolutely destroyed her.
I think you guys did it.
Well, well, well, looks like you numbnuts managed to scrape up 15 points in round 1.
50 points! 50 points! 50 points!
Points! 15! 15 points! 54!
That's 54 in the middle! Yeah, 50, not 53! 54!
Alright, alright, gear up for Round 2!
Okay, okay, okay. Give us the balloon!
Is Gigi on guard? Is Gigi cheating?
What?
Turn around, turn around.
Alright, let's put your blindfold on. Okay, help me please.
Alright, alright. Let's put your blindfold on.
Are you thinking on perfect?
Is it on? Yes, it's on. Okay, now.
Can you see anything? Watch this.
There you go. Okay, I'm ready.
Let's fight! Hit!
Okay, okay. Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, hit!
Took you buttercups long enough. Now square up!
Alright, are they here? Gigi, count us down!
I'm going to count down!
Three!
Two!
One!
Bend, swing, one!
And two!
Faster, two! Faster, harder!
And three! Faster, harder! And four! Faster, harder!
And five!
Okay, turn around. Left, round her, left, left, left!
Left, left. Oh, she's tripped. She's bent over. She's bent over.
Stop! That was a ground! That was a ground!
Go, go, go, go! Go, behind! Okay!
Faster, boys! Faster, boys! Hit!
Not there! Where did you go?
Cecilia, where did you go? Don't follow me! Raora, straight ahead, straight ahead, straight ahead!
Go right! Straight! Straight! Keep it straight! Keep it straight!
Keep it straight! Keep it straight! Keep it straight! Get her! Get her!
Go low! Go low! Go low, go low, go low!
Go low! Go low! Go round! Go round!
Hit! Hit! Hit! Hit!
Forward! Forward! Stay where you are!
Okay, now, now, now, now, now! Go low! Hit! Hit!
Oh gosh! Hit! Hit! Hit! Hit!
I don't understand! What are you saying?
Forward! Straight! Straight! Straight! Wait, wait, wait!
Okay, okay, don't hit me! Don't hit me!
Raora, forward! Get up! Raora, get up!
Oh my gosh! That was... That was something. That was...
Gigi, score!
15 points!
That was very dizzy. I'm dizzy, I'm dizzy, I'm dizzy.
I am... I am scared of the darkness.
It is okay. You're still my pretty kitty. You're still my pretty kitty.
Your third trial is behind that door. What's the password?!
Oh really? I can do it. Together. Up together.
It's 88008!
Open!
Whoa! So cool! So cool! Yes! So cool! Yeah!
Let's go, everyone! Hazah!
At attention, you dogs! It's time for your third trial!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a second. No one said anything about a life-threatening challenge.
My hearing is okay.
Don't worry about it. You're not going to kill us, right?
Roara, rules!
Okay, so number one: Balance the blocks while stacking them according to the color order on the instructions.
There are 5 levels, and you earn the same numbers of points as the level you clear.
But watch out: the higher the level, the tougher the challenge! If you mess up the placement and the bomb explodes, it's game over, so, yeah, you lose, game over.
Whoa.
Alright, who's ready to get SMOKED?
Do you want to go first? Die! Yeah, you should go first.
I will take the first bomb.
I will die for justice! For justice! For justice!
Welcome to Justice!
You got 10 seconds to survive levels 1 and 2,
then 30 seconds for levels 3 through 5.
10 seconds? Can you count?
That's nine more than one.
You got this!
10 times one, guys!
Can you count to 10? You at home, can you count to 10?
One, two...
No, no, no! It's not time yet!
Okay, okay, calm down, let's start.
GG, ready? I'm ready!
Three, two, one, go!
That's red and purple!
I am the purple!
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, easy, easy.
Oh, good job!
You good? GG!
That's close!
How do you do that?
Oh, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Green, go!
All of them! All of them!
Four seconds! That's impossible!
Oh, no! Ah...
They were so far away from each other!
We always believed in you!
GG, GG!
Red! Okay, this one you will have to do like a... thingy at the end.
Yellow, purple, okay.
She's doing it!
White! Woo!
Now pose to disarm the bomb!
Wait!
Hey, that's pretty good!
10 seconds! You gotta keep it! Keep it!
GG did really good, GG! Really good!
Well, good job, good job.
That's a difficult one! Put purple on...
Why'd the ghosts do that?
This is not shameless bribery!
It's really good!
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
One-one was a race horse, two-two was one-two. One-one-one-one race, two-two one-one-two.
She defused it though!
Nice one, GG!
What? Holy moly!
Why'd they put this one so far?
20 seconds is a long time!
You can do it! You can make it!
What is this?
Oh, she's doing really well!
GG, go!
That's it!
Four...
Oh no!
GG, 2 seconds!
Are you okay, GG?
Yeah, she died for justice!
She's deceased!
GG, are you okay?
Don't worry, she's just being mean to you.
It's okay.
You're gonna be fine!
Put that in fair!
Put that in fair. Hey, she could do math in 2 seconds!
That's not fair!
Quick math!
Hey, you did amazing though!
Side for justice!
It's okay, you did...
GG, what are you doing?
Smells like a barbecue in here...
You got 10 points!
10!
Did she even count that high?
10 times 1, that's 10!
Oh, who's next?
Someone else is gonna be... get blowed up, right?
That's enough, chatterboxes! You're up, Raora.
And then once you become a burn victim, like GG...
What? But I licked her again!
She licked us clean!
She licked us clean, GG. Look at that!
I'm so proud of you, GG! I'm ready to disarm the bomb.
You got this!
You got this, Raora!
Best! Level 1!
And in 3, 2, 1, go!
Light blue! Easy, easy! Got this! Got this!
Purple! Got this! Tadan!
Ah, good job!
Good! Easy!
Woah, that's a lot of colors! Crazy!
What the... No, no, no! Over there! Green!
Yay!
I knew Smokey was nice!
Level 3! See the colors? Purple...
Okay, it's party, party, party!
You have a lot of time, don't worry.
There's a lot of time!
Got this, got this, got this!
Okay!
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!
[Level 3: Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!]
You have to do a full-on...
Now what up?
Move many for my leg.
You just do the pose, you can do whatever pose you want!
What? What?!
Oh, okay!
Whoa, hi!
Man, I finally make her do those poses, huh? Huh?
Yay, was that cute?
Ah yeah, very cute!
I'm out of the way! Oh, and time we can huddle.
Get up, get up. Really good. No!
Wrong color. Wait, that's the wrong color.
Wrong color!
Oh, she got this! She got this! She got this!
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
[Level 4: Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!]
How much wood would a woodchuck chuck, if a woodchuck could chuck wood!
Yay!
Purple!
Pink!
We don't need that when we're catching criminals.
Oh yeah, we don't.
There's so many colors.
That's a lot of colors.
Okay, that's a lot of color.
Okay, okay, okay.
Yellow, yellow, black, blue.
Yellow is there! Almost finished.
Oh, dark blue! Wait, dark blue! Oh, oh, oh, no, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine.
Oh, dark blue! Wait, dark blue! Oh, it's fine.
Okay, 35 plus 6 is 41!
41!
Whoa!
She got that so quick.
I'm so good, I'm...
Wait, her math question is so much shorter!
Big cat means big brain! Big cat! Big brain! Woo!
I can for everyone. Pet, pet, pet, pet, pet, pet, pet, pet...
I can for everyone. Pet, pet, pet, pet, pet, pet...
Raora scored 15 points. Not bad for a blockhead.
Job, thanks.
Good job, thanks.
Thanks.
Yatta! Yatta!
I'm all fired up, I'm ready!
Ow!
Stop fighting, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
You know what, shut up! Shut up! You can't speak, do you mind, please?
You know what, shut up! Shut up! Can you calm down, please?
Okay, thank you.
Three, two, one, go!
Go!
Why? It's a traffic cone.
Go, sis, it's to go! Go, go, go!
Woah, it's so flat.
That's like a a candy.
That's hard to balance. It's hard to balance.
Yay! Good job!
Go, sis, it's to go!
Okay, purple corn.
That's too many corn.
That's okay.
Purple, yellow.
Whew!
You got it!
Yay! Got it! Okay.
Okay.
Oh, that looks so yummy.
This looks so good. Red, yellow, red.
Red can't I can't I can't. Color blind!
Red, can't, I can't. Color blind!
You can't. Ah!
Ah, got it!
You got it! Bring it. Bring it.
Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!
[Level 3: Now, pose to disarm the bomb!!]
Oh, what's your pose?
Pose with the left or the right up.
Oh, I'm so relaxed.
A monster!
10 seconds left.
Now breathe in. Hold it! Hold it! Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
Woo!
Yeah, okay. Red.
Can do it, can do it.
Green, red, don't want green.
Yellow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you're bringing over every single color.
The strategy, the strategy.
Balance, balance.
Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!
[Level 4: Disarm the bomb with a tongue twister!]
The big black bug bit the big black bear, but the big black bear bit the big black bug back.
Yay! Okay.
Leave your tongue stuttering.
Go, go!
Woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah, woah. Nice! That was really funny.
Woah, woah, woah, woah, woah. Nice! That was really funny.
Nice, nice. You got it.
Nice, nice, guys. Yeah, yeah.
Get white, white, blue. To win now.
Purple. Woah. Rumble down.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Get it. Get it. Oh, that's black.
Oh my god. Oh my god.
It's so over.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Color blind! Color blind! Color blind!
I'm colour blind!
You can't see me, right?
I love zombies.
Did you look did you look?
Open your eyes! You've got to face your fears!
Woo!
Nice and smokey... 10 points!
I got ten!
And can you can you count?
Do you count to 10?
Do you count 10?
How many fingers am I holding up?
At least four. At least at least four.
At least four. At least four.
Queen!
Lead off justice!
We'll take on this challenge.
Yes! It's time!
Justice!
Show you what I'm made of! Let's start! All right, all right.
Pass. Okay, I didn't get to the math.
We'll make it even so it's fair. All right.
Oh, these blocks are quite far away.
Ah, right. Let us put them together. Right. Fine. Bring it on! Bring it on!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes.
Are you ready, Liz? We're going to count down.
Are you okay?
I'm ready!
All right, level one.
Yes.
Three! Two! One! Stop!
Oh, that's easy. Come on, come on. You got this.
Okay, she got this, she got this. She got this.
Oh, the black ones are so far away.
She got it. She got it. She got it. She got it. Let's go! Woohoo!
Haha!
Uh-oh. Okay. Okay.
No, no. That one's good. Far. Oh, blues!
That one's there. That one's there.
Got it! Defused!
All right. Yes. Haha!
That's a pyramid.
That pyramid screen. You got this.
I bought- sell- sell you.
And then you sell it. Or someone got it.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Go.
Go! Go! Stairs! Stairs! Stairs! You got this! You got this! You got this!
What are you doing? What are you doing? Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Okay!
Now pose, Simon.
Oh.
Yeah. Oh.
These poses not seem fair.
Yeah, this pose. Any cool pose? Ooh.
That's your coolest pose. Wow.
Why does she get yoga and they just get whatever they want? Yoga, and they get photoshoot.
Oh gosh.
Got this. Okay.
She got this. She thought this.
Nice, pink.
Got this.
Oh, she's got that's our queen.
That's our queen.
All right.
Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear. Fuzzy Wuzzy had no hair. Fuzzy Wuzzy wasn't fuzzy, was he?
Whaty Wuy?
I'm glad you're wuy.
Wuzzy Wuzzy was there. Fuzzy Wuzzy was a bear.
Fuzzy Wuzzy... I can't remember the rest. Boots and cats and boots and cats...
Fuzzy Wuzzy... he's there... didn't see him anywhere. Yeah, I'm the queen of justice.
And uh, what rhymes with
That's just- you know what rhymes with justice? Think about it. Just I
Get out of here.
Yeah, just eyes.
All right.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Difficult.
And the light one.
And then I need the pink one and the blue one. Wait, no, I don't need this blue one.
Get that out of here.
Purple, light blue, purple.
Got it! Got it!
Okay, this one.
I need this one and I need...
Got it! Got it! No! No! No!
Everything's falling apart.
No, it's fine! It's not falling apart!
No, you can do it, you can still do it!
I get it?
No.
Get on.
Oh, dynamite!
Defused!
What the frig?
Get out. Get out of here.
That's fine.
I mean.
Yeah, that's fine.
Well, whatever.
It's it's I- I got
Kick them! Kick them! Get out your earpiece!
I didn't- I didn't want to do math anyway.
It's fine. I didn't want to do math anyway.
It's fine. It's fine.
I got some math for you... 10 points!
10 points! Yay!
Simmer down, buttercups! You still got the final trial!
Quizzes and tests?
We don't want to do math anymore!
We just want to relax. I'm getting tired.
Yeah.
Let's go. Let's go.
My queen, my queen.
Let's go. I want ice cream now.
Bye.
What the frig?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'm the only one still burnt up!
Hey, can I go- can I go shower real quick before the next- next game?
Taking you up low, taking you up be-
Haha!
All right. All showered up. I don't smell like a cheeky chicken, well, burnt cheeky chicken anymore. Haha!
Oh, maybe they're hiding.
All right, I know a way to bring them out.
Justice, just like that!
Justice! Get, get down! You were hiding this whole time. Oh, goodness!
Hello, pretty kitty!
I'll pick it, I'll pick it!
All right.
It's time for the final trial, twerps! Cecilia, rules!
Okay! Yes, sir!
The final trial is Hammer of Justice! Whack-a-Gnome!
Whack-a-gnome.
Number one: Defeat the evil gnomes emerging from the wall by striking them with a giant hammer!
Number one: Defeat the evil gnomes emerging
from the wall with a giant hammer!
Not all gnomes are bad! Some are friendly, some are nice.
Not all gnomes are bad! Some are friendly,
some are nice.
So be careful not to hit the good ones and only hit the bad ones.
So be careful not to hit the good ones
and only hit the bad ones.
Smash a bad gnome = +3 points / Hit a good gnome = -3 points
Aim carefully to maximize your score!
Okay, so we're supposed to hit the bad ones.
Right, okay. I just need to know.
We'll be able to tell. Okay, okay. And then be careful to aim carefully!
We'll be able to tell. Okay, okay.
And then aim carefully!
And then at the end, how many points can you score in 30 seconds?
And then at the end, how many points
can you score in 30 seconds?
30 seconds!
So they come out of the holes, and then you have to hit them, and then there's good gnomes and bad gnomes.
So they come out of the holes and you have
to hit them—good gnomes and bad gnomes.
If I can't tell, I just—are you a bad gnome?
Here's the bad dude you gotta feed to the worms!
Here's the bad dude you gotta feed
to the worms!
Sunglasses inside!
And then there's one of the bad ones.
And this is the good one. No friendly fire!
That's a good one. That's a good one. Okay, okay.
That's a good one. That's a good one.
Okay, okay.
Red-headed gnome sunglasses good, not to kena. That's a good one.
Red-headed gnome sunglasses good,
not to kena. That's a good one.
And the cat's a good gnome, so don't hit this gnome!
And the cat's a good gnome,
so don't hit this gnome!
Okay, okay, okay.
All right, put those muscles to work, big cat.
All right, put those muscles to work,
big cat.
I got this one, guys! I got two! I got two!
Oh! Well, there it is. Oh, come on, Pretty Kitty, it can't weigh that much!
Oh! Well, there it is. Oh, come on,
Pretty Kitty, it can't weigh that much!
You're gonna have to escalate it to get to five.
You're gonna have to escalate
it to get to five.
Come on! You can do it! Believe in me, who believes in thee! Let my voice be your strength, Pretty Kitty, use your god eyes!
Come on! You can do it! Believe in me
who believes in thee! Let my voice be your strength!
Stop this!
Ah! I can do it!
I can do it!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! I'm scared!
Ready to roll?
I am ready.
I have the power of justice and cute girls!
I have the power of justice
and cute girls!
I can do it! You got this! I can do it!
All right, it's time to whack a gnome! Are you ready?
All right, it's time to whack a gnome!
Are you ready?
Yes! I'm ready!
I'm ready!
30 seconds! Go! One!
Two!
Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes!
Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes!
Hit the gnomes!
I'm scared! She's close to us! Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes!
I'm scared! She's close to us!
Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes!
I don't know how to- Kill the gnomes! Oh, gosh! The cucumber!
I don't know how to—kill the gnomes!
Oh, gosh! The cucumber!
Oh, no! Oh! She's killing them! Oh, gosh!
Oh, no! Oh! She's killing them!
Oh, gosh!
Disgusting! Disgusting! Disgusting!
Why did you hit the cucumber?
That's a cucumber!
Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes! Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes!
Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes!
Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes!
I don't know how to deal about this! Kill the gnomes!
I don't know how to deal with this!
Kill the gnomes!
Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes! Oh, gosh! It's disgusting!
Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes!
Oh, gosh! It's disgusting!
Why did you hit the cucumber?
That's a cucumber!
Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes!
Kill the gnomes! Kill the gnomes!
I don't know how to feel about this! Hit the gnomes!
I don't know how to feel about this!
Hit the gnomes!
Oh, gosh! That's a cucumber!
Oh, no! That's a cucumber! Disgusting!
Disgusting! Disgusting!
Why did you hit the cucumber? That's a cucumber!
Why did you hit the cucumber?
That's a cucumber!
Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes! Oh! Oh, jeez!
Hit the gnomes! Hit the gnomes!
Oh! Oh, jeez!
What was that? That was not a gnome!
That was a weird green gnome, huh? Disgusting!
That was a weird green gnome, huh?
Disgusting!
Oopsie daisy... I forgot to mention hitting cucumbers give you 5 points per hit.
Oopsie daisy... I forgot to mention
hitting cucumbers give you 5 points per hit.
Really?
Boy!
She kind of did everything!
I feel like you should have said that earlier. She got so many points then, probably.
I feel like you should have said that earlier.
She got so many points then, probably!
Total scores will be tallied at the end of the game. Which one of you meatheads is next? Move out!
Total scores will be tallied at the end of the game.
Which one of you meatheads is next? Move out!
Who's next? Who's next? Who's next?
Liz, I think it's your turn now.
Oh! Well, okay then. Let me just take off my jacket, all right. Flame off! Let's go!
Oh! Well, okay then. Let me just take off
my jacket, all right. Flame off! Let's go!
All right, let me go get the... the hammer over here.
Time to earn your title, "leader!"
All right, are you ready, Liz?
I am ready.
Okay.
Countdown. Three, two, one, go! 30 seconds!
Countdown. Three, two, one, go!
30 seconds!
Oh, crazy! She's going! That's the leader of Justice, after all!
Oh, crazy! She's going!
That's the leader of Justice, after all!
She's one second per hammer swing. Hit the bad one!
She's one second per hammer swing.
Hit the bad one!
Say it was heavy?
She's built for this.
She does that every day.
Oh, uh, I mean it's, you know, not as heavy as Dawn, but...
You can do this, Gigi! Come on, Gigi! Come on!
All right, just lift with your legs! Lift with your legs!
Use your legs! Use your legs! What the... Use your legs!
We're done, we're done.
Look at her lives! She's stronger than this!
Look at her life! She's stronger than this!
All right, Gigi! Break her leg! Or break a gnome, in this case.
Thank you.
All right, here we go.
Three! Two! One! Start!
No! No! Gigi, Gigi, that's the wrong one! That's the wrong color, Gigi!
Elizabeth: Wait, Gigi, that's not... That's how it works? Oh no! That's the wrong color, Gigi!
Gigi, that's the wrong color! Pick out the colors! Pick out the purple one! Just the purple one!
I'm ready! I'm ready! I'm ready! I'm ready! I'm ready!
Oh well, she got the cucumber.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No, I know what I must do.
Gigi? What are you doing? Why are you looking at me like this? Gigi?
Gigi! No, no, no, no, no! What are you doing? No, no, no, no, no!
Why can't I hit her?
Oh, she's so good!
Oh!
I should learn that.
So good.
That seems like a good dodge move.
Dodge! Dodge! Dodge!
Hey, what's wrong with the cucumber thing?
You must teach me that move sometime.
I will do it.
Hey, when it jumps like that, it's cute.
I don't know what happened.
I just love consciousness.
That cucumber has... That was really impressive.
Things!
Button those lips! Cecilia! Get in there!
Okay, I'm ready. Avenge me.
Oh wait, you need the hammer.
Let's cheer for Ceci, okay?
Okay.
Here we go. It's time to whack a gnome!
Three! Two! One! Go!
You know what, Smokey? You know what you are doing to us the entire time?
Yeah, you're trying to make us play games, but I'm not going to play your game! And I'm not going to play into your gnomes either!
Cause I do not discriminate! We need to hit all of them! He's going to start discriminating again!
We need to cut them! He's on the exterior!
All right.
God! Hit them! You're so far out! Hit them! Go, go, go! Hit them!
Sorry. Sorry. I've had enough.
I've had enough, Smokey. You're pitting us against each other, but we will not play your games any longer!
We'll happily play your games. Yeah, we'll happily play your... No, this is just a joke, you know.
Funny, you know. We have humor too, not just Sremm, but... You okay?
Goin' AWOL, huh!? 0 points, you slug!
I don't want it anymore! You make us sports the entire time! I'm sick of this!
It's okay. Hey, hey. I'm sorry.
Enough of you.
It's okay. I got you.
Why do you keep falling on Smokey, cry?
Find it somehow. Can we escalate this?
Wait, we need to stop this.
Hey, stop, stop, stop, stop!
You hit me!
I'm sorry, Smokey.
We make sure that this is not going to happen again. We're sorry! We're sorry! We're sorry!
So... So what's the highest score?
Just tell us. Tell us, Smokey.
Come on, Smokey. Come on.
End this pain.
After four trials, one of you clowns came on top...
The winner is... Raora Panthera! You win, cupcake!
Yay! I pretty can! Good job, good job, good job!
Good kitty, good kitty!
Yours is a little cat ears!
Zip it! It's time for our winner to make her little announcement.
As we did announcement, we'll be performing the new song right now! Right now!
Yay! So geezer, are you ready? Yeah! It's going to be so nice.
We'll be practicing our singing and dancing really, really hard to perform for everyone today, so make sure to watch our very first live performance...
Ready, set!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis I'm
Infamous, yeah I get a little villainous
Look into my eyes
I'll seek you out
Reveal the truth and lies that you just can't hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by a chain, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of a devastating force is coming
Out of my veins, feel my pulse it's rising and igniting
Fire
Snuff it out
Walking the line, on the edge of becoming what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, renegade
Walking the line, fell so far
into poison and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade
Don't care at all
I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out
Make 'em fall down
Make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down
Then they crash
Make 'em fall down
Make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down
Then they crash
Bound by a vow, can I tread the waters lightly never
Making a sound, incognito dio light the pathway
making a sound, incognito, light the pathway.
Burning 'em out, in the fallout I'll stand in the ashes
Fire
Snuff it out
Walking the line, on the edge of becoming what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, renegade
Walking the line, fell so far
into poison and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade
Don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis I'm
Infamous, yeah I get a little villainous
Walking the line, fell so far
into poison and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade
Everyone, Nima!
What did you think of our performance?
Yeah! Make sure to stream Renegade! Let's get us to number one!
And make sure to stream Renegade! Let's get us to number one!
And also guys, be sure to remember, share your thoughts, screenshots and framed moments from today's training and live performance with the hashtag Justice3D!
And also guys, be sure to remember to share your thoughts, screenshots, and favorite moments from today's training and live performance with the hashtag #Justice3D!
Oh, it's an alarm! Oh no!
Please, put it in emergency and let's take a look.
Oh yes, you're right! You're right Raora!
All right, everyone come over. Let's take a look.
What do you think if we go to the stage we can catch them? Mookie! Mookie!
We wanna go to their arena...
Yes, yes!
All you punks think about is standin' on stage! Go, get out of my face! And make sure you catch Advent!
We'll give them a taste of their own medicine, right guys?
Let's go!
Just like that! Just like that!
Head of us! Go, go, go, go, get out of here!
Where are they? I've been here 5 hours now... I'm 5 hours!
6 hours maybe!
We did it, we're here! You're so slow! What do you mean you're so slow? You're so far!
Well, I had to take a shower, you know.
Cucumber, that's me.
Well, where are they? They're gone!
They're gone! Maybe because you guys are too slow.
You'll see them? No. Aha!
Aha, I see how it is.
Well, you know... maybe we should perform the song we all worked so hard practicing!
That sounds like a great idea! All right, let's get in positions everyone!
In positions! 1, 2, 3, 4, let's go!
Te wo agete
Raise your hands,
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands across the sea,
Clap your hands todo kimasu you ni
Clap your hands so they reach across,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hora issho ni everybody
Look, together with everybody!
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands beyond the sky,
Clap your hands hibiki masu you ni
Clap your hands so they echo through,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hikari sasu boku-tachi no mirai
Toward our light-filled future!
5 4 3 2 1
Hololive 5th stars
Hajime you ka saa diving
Shall we start by diving in?
Matte mo im in ai timing
Waiting won't bring the right timing,
Ano sakana mitai ni
Like that fish,
Swimming swimming
Hikiyoseru no lighting
Drawing in the lighting,
Mada mienai yo maybe
Still can't see it yet, maybe?
Kono saki ni wa nani ga aru no?
What lies ahead of us here?
Mada hayai yo take it
It's still too early, take it easy,
Oitsuku made shaking
Shaking until we catch up,
Demo tamani tomatte thinking thinking
But sometimes stopping to think, think!
Kaete miseru change
We'll show you we can change,
Fumi dasu no sa stepping
Stepping forward as we go,
Tsukan de miseru yo kira kira my dream
We'll grab hold of my sparkling dream!
Kanau hi made story tsunagu kara
Connecting the story until the day it comes true,
Datte kimi ni zutto mite hoshii kara
Because I want you to keep watching me all along!
Te wo agete
Raise your hands,
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands across the sea,
Clap your hands todo kimasu you ni
Clap your hands so they reach across,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hora issho ni everybody
Look, together with everybody!
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands beyond the sky,
Clap your hands hibiki masu you ni
Clap your hands so they echo through,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hikari sasu boku-tachi no mirai
Toward our light-filled future!
Kyou wa iranai bure iki
No need for breaks today,
Risei kowa se breaking
Breaking down reason,
Nanji demo ii desho? shirokujichuu kimi wa nani wo feeling
Any time is fine, right? 24/7 what are you feeling?
Tokihanate sparking
Unleash the sparking,
Kurayami ni hanatsu laser beam
Unleashing laser beams into the darkness!
Hikara sete stage tsukuru kara
Making the stage shine as we build it,
Datte kimi ni motto mite hoshii kara
Because I want you to watch me even more!
Te wo agete
Raise your hands,
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands across the sea,
Clap your hands todo kimasu you ni
Clap your hands so they reach across,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hora issho ni everybody
Look, together with everybody!
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands beyond the sky,
Clap your hands hibiki masu you ni
Clap your hands so they echo through,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Kasanaru wave sekai wo yurase
Overlapping waves, make the world shake!
1,2,3,4,5,6 do it!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, do it!
Owari ga aru koto kurai sudeni i know
I already know that everything has an end,
Demo mada mada oyogi tarinai no
But I still haven't had enough of swimming!
give me crazy
marude lazy?
Acting all lazy?
jigen mazariau no
Dimensions are mixing together,
Subete nuri kaeru blue
Repainting everything in blue!
Te wo agete
Raise your hands,
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands across the sea,
Clap your hands todo kimasu you ni
Clap your hands so they reach across,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hora issho ni everybody
Look, together with everybody!
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands beyond the sky,
Clap your hands hibiki masu you ni
Clap your hands so they echo through,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hikari sasu boku-tachi no mirai
Toward our light-filled future!
Kyou wa iranai bure iki
No need for breaks today,
Risei kowa se breaking
Breaking down reason,
Nanji demo ii desho? shirokujichuu kimi wa nani wo feeling
Any time is fine, right? 24/7 what are you feeling?
Te wo agete
Raise your hands,
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands across the sea,
Clap your hands todo kimasu you ni
Clap your hands so they reach across,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hora issho ni everybody
Look, together with everybody!
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands beyond the sky,
Clap your hands hibiki masu you ni
Clap your hands so they echo through,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hikari sasu boku-tachi no mirai
Toward our light-filled future!
Te wo agete
Raise your hands,
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands across the sea,
Clap your hands todo kimasu you ni
Clap your hands so they reach across,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hora issho ni everybody
Look, together with everybody!
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands beyond the sky,
Clap your hands hibiki masu you ni
Clap your hands so they echo through,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Kasanaru wave sekai wo yurase
Overlapping waves, make the world shake!
Te wo agete
Raise your hands,
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands across the sea,
Clap your hands todo kimasu you ni
Clap your hands so they reach across,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hora issho ni everybody
Look, together with everybody!
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands beyond the sky,
Clap your hands hibiki masu you ni
Clap your hands so they echo through,
Te wo tatakou te wo tatakou
Let's clap our hands, let's clap our hands,
Hikari sasu boku-tachi no mirai
Toward our light-filled future!
Look up at the horizon together as one
A star is on the rise and it's only begun
The pivotal moment we're clamoring for
An infinite future's at our door, yeah
It's a timeless story with a new feel
Not just allegory, it's real
Wake up, big dreams about to come true
That means it's time to break through
Never knew we could make it so far,
But we're striving, thriving, here we are
Achieving the impossible, we're virtually unstoppable
We can't sit still, we just keep moving!
We're making our way to the next dimension,
We'll reinvent the world that we live in
We'll greet every day with new intentions
Break conventions, run right through!
Been smashing barriers left and right
Strong as we ever were, scaling heights
So get together, let's reunite!
Reach up, reach out, the future's bright.
We've been together for what feels like an eternity, the times are changing, but we're ready for infinity
We've been together for what feels like an eternity,
the times are changing, but we're ready for infinity
Our stories align, we're gonna go far when we combine
So look at the horizon and then look beyond,
We'll marvel at the skies and the strength of our bond,
We're making a vow to the smiling stars, a powerful moment that's all ours
We're making a vow to the smiling stars,
a powerful moment that's all ours
The seasons change, but we keep shining
Now everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension,
A million thrills in every direction
We'll give every mile our full attention,
Breaking tension, breaking through!
With endless energy, stronger ties
A perfect harmony we devise
So clap along with me
The future's right before our eyes.
A new dimension of freedom that we've found, yeah, we've made it
A new dimension of freedom that we've found,
yeah, we've made it
We're breaking out of the mold, no longer bound, we're unlimited
We're breaking out of the mold, no longer bound,
we're unlimited
We're gonna spring to life and break the chains
Turn up the hype, can't be contained
We're shaking up the status quo, no time to stop, we're good to go!
We're shaking up the status quo,
no time to stop, we're good to go!
The whole wide world is listening, so everybody sing!
The whole wide world is listening,
so everybody sing!
We're making our way to the next dimension,
We're living out the dreams we believe in
Excitement beyond our comprehension, there's no question we'll break through!
Excitement beyond our comprehension,
there's no question we'll break through!
We'll keep aspiring to excel
It's awe-inspiring, going well
So light the fire and let's rebel!
The future's brighter, we can tell!
Yeah!
Amazing job today!
We conquered all trials and performed the full song!
Just us! Justice! Just like that, we stick together!
Not done yet! We have not one, but two big announcements!
Drum roll, please...
Introducing the official Justice 3D Showcase celebration merch!
Alright everyone, get into your match position!
First, we have Sergeant Smokey Multi Case!
Now then, this is for you,
so handy items to store your favorite goodies.
On the left side, you can keep button badges and keychains.
The right side fits smaller acrylic stand-up cards!
Yeah!
It's also hooked on the back to attach even more keychains.
And we'd be so happy if you show off our merch at events, please!
Thank you so much!
Yay! Yay!
All right, Raora, your turn, next one.
My turn.
All right, everyone, next one is...
The life-sized 3D acrylic stand!
Life-sized!
Life-sized, baby!
I was like, "Wait, life-sized? That was my fault."
I didn't remember it off the start. That's true.
I didn't remember it after I repeated it and I was like, "Wait, life-sized?"
Life-sized!
Big cut means big acrylic.
Oh, yeah! That's big though.
Big acrylic! Life-sized!
In fact, Justice is coming to life as 3D acrylic stands!
Everyone loves acrylic stands, right?
I love them. I love them.
Whether you have a room dedicated to acrylic stands or just starting your collection,
you are going to need all of Justice, okay?
Get them all! All of them!
Next one.
What's that?
Oh, it's me!
Okay, and...
as we all mentioned during our 3D showcases,
we each have our own merch too, ooh la la!
All right, then I will start.
This right here is the paper knife and acrylic stand.
It's a lovely set inspired by the design of my sword, Thorn!
Yeah!
This paper knife can actually be displayed by resting it on the acrylic stand.
It's so cool!
You all, you all get your own Thorn!
No, no, no, baby Thorn!
So cute!
Oh, gosh, I can't, I can't.
It's so cool! You go, you go, you go!
And now...
Hand in Cushion for Grab!
Do you remember seeing it? Sadly, there is no...
oogly's on to show you how soft and fluffy it is,
but it is very fluffy and it's made from a very...
squishy material.
You'll never want to stop squeezing it!
You want to stop squeezing it! I'm going to squeeze this!
Squeezing it is so cute and it's a crab!
Yay!
Cecilia!
Whoa! Cecilia!
It's Pouch & Socks set!
And do you want the sock? Monday, Tuesday, every day of the week, seven pairs of socks! And then you have your little pouch, the little Tomo pouch to put in your socks.
Yeah, um, it's really cute. You can put anything in it, of course, not only socks, but yeah, I really like it. It's so little Tomo and it reminds me of the Tomo pouch I made once.
I like it a lot!
Yeah! Please get it! Yay!
Okay, Dora, you can put your toes in your ultimate toe socks.
It's my turn.
And this is Raora's pencil case and keychain set.
It's me wearing a Tettino costume and I'll be so happy if you feel it. It's so cute.
You like it?
Yeah!
I'll be so happy if you feel it with lots of stationery and use it at school or in the office or really anywhere you want.
And the keychain can be attached to the pencil case, so you clip it into your bag or anything you like.
Very cute!
Cute! Very cute!
With a little metino!
Yeah!
Everything's really cute.
I'm so excited to see you guys...
Excited to see all of Justice's merch. And if you want to know when can we purchase them?
Well, they will all be available to purchase right after this stream! So make sure to grab them ASAP! And that's our merch announcement!
Yeah! Wow!
That's the first one, and...
And as Cece just mentioned, there is one more announcement.
And you all know, Justice will be performing live for the very first time at thehololive 3rd Concert!
Taking place at the Radiance City Musical in New York on August 23rd and 24th, PDT!
And right after this stream, we will be redirecting you into the music video premiere!
Justice also is in there, of course, and maybe maybe you'll see some...
maybe you'll see us doing some stuff?
Who knows? You'll have to wait. We'll be moving and grooving, baby!
So make sure to stay tuned, it's going to be very, very soon.
Gosh! All right, everyone.
She's getting a little sad,
but it's almost time to say goodbye.
Before we go, let's each share our thoughts and thank all our fans for their support.
Before we go, let's each share our thoughts
and thank all our fans for their support.
Uh, Gigi, you go first.
Grams, thank you so much for supporting us all this time!
Grams, thank you so much
for supporting us all this time!
And can you believe it's been a little over a year now, and so many more years with just chats, Justice, and Grams! Yay!
And can you believe it's been a little over a year
now? And so many more years with Just Chats, Justice, and Grams! Yay!
Gosh,
Hello, thank you so much!
Gosh, Rosarians, give me a mighty huzzah!
We did it! Oh my gosh, thank you so much for joining all of us on our adventure here.
We did it! Oh my gosh, thank you so much
for joining all of us on our adventure here.
I— I can't believe it! Oh my gosh, we're 3D now!
I— I can't believe it!
Oh my gosh, we're 3D now!
And we're going to be in a concert, and everything's happening, like all our dreams is coming true!
And we're going to be in a concert,
and everything's happening, like all our dreams are coming true!
It's all thanks to you guys! Thank you so so much! Onwards, and upwards, and huzzah!
It's all thanks to you guys!
Thank you so, so much! Onwards, and upwards, and huzzah!
Thank you very much! Thank you so much, everyone! Thank you, just chats!
Thank you very much!
Thank you so much, everyone! Thank you, Just Chats!
Thank you, too! Thank you, everyone!
Thank you, Justice, of course! It's been a lot of fun, we worked very hard, and I'm so excited and happy that you all got to see it finally.
Thank you, Justice, of course! It's been a lot of fun,
we worked very hard, and I'm so excited and happy
that you all got to see it finally.
And...
Thank you from the bottom of our hearts for supporting us thus far! Please keep supporting us from onwards, thank you!
Thank you from the bottom of our hearts
for supporting us thus far!
Please keep supporting us onwards, thank you!
To Tini, Torata, Toratatatad!
Thank you so much for supporting Justice for a whole year, and many more to come!
Thank you so much for supporting Justice
for a whole year, and many more to come!
This— This has been a dream come true for me, being in 3D, dancing with you guys, and having so much fun.
This— This has been a dream come true for me,
being in 3D, dancing with you guys,
and having so much fun.
So, I really really appreciate it. Thank you so much from the bottom of my heart. Big cat means...
So, I really, really appreciate it.
Thank you so much from the bottom of my heart.
Big cat means...
Big Justice!
Once again, thank you all for watching our very first 3D collab stream today!
Once again, thank you all for watching
our very first 3D collab stream today!
Please keep supporting Justice! Justice, just like that!
Please keep supporting Justice!
Justice, just like that!
Justice! Get-get-tah!
Justice!
Get-get-tah!